{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597478057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597478057"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597483782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597483781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597487288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597487288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597492720","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597492720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597497851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597497851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597500962","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597500962"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597503730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597503730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597506609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597506609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597512007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597512007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597516875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597516875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597519858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597519857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597523259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597523258"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597526508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597526508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597529616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597529616"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597532412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597532412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597535588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597535588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597538964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597538964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597542185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597542185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597545400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597545399"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597548666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597548666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597551677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597551677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597554594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597554594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597557388","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597557388"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597560467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597560467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597563560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597563559"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597566250","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597566250"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597572003","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597572003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 78716b84-03dc-4feb-9526-97c1ce4ff797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597581740","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597581739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 1464f0f9-ef82-40c9-85dc-fd6df3157f74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597587328","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597587328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 1464f0f9-ef82-40c9-85dc-fd6df3157f74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597592293","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597592292"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 1464f0f9-ef82-40c9-85dc-fd6df3157f74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597599842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597599841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 1464f0f9-ef82-40c9-85dc-fd6df3157f74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597605450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597605450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 1464f0f9-ef82-40c9-85dc-fd6df3157f74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_9-10-15"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597611537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597611537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 1464f0f9-ef82-40c9-85dc-fd6df3157f74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-13-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597618122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597618121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 1464f0f9-ef82-40c9-85dc-fd6df3157f74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597624056","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597624056"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 1464f0f9-ef82-40c9-85dc-fd6df3157f74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-13"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597629004","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597629004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 1464f0f9-ef82-40c9-85dc-fd6df3157f74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_4-12-13"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597634465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597634465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 1464f0f9-ef82-40c9-85dc-fd6df3157f74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_0-1-10"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597640312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597640312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 1464f0f9-ef82-40c9-85dc-fd6df3157f74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-13-6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597646084","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597646084"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 1464f0f9-ef82-40c9-85dc-fd6df3157f74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-11-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597652711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597652709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 1464f0f9-ef82-40c9-85dc-fd6df3157f74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-11-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597661515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597661515"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" a7017fec-5d4d-49d7-8262-3da7786c65fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597664806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597664805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" a7017fec-5d4d-49d7-8262-3da7786c65fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597668091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597668091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" a7017fec-5d4d-49d7-8262-3da7786c65fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597679063","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597679063"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" a7017fec-5d4d-49d7-8262-3da7786c65fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597682398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597682398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" a7017fec-5d4d-49d7-8262-3da7786c65fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597686086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597686085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" a7017fec-5d4d-49d7-8262-3da7786c65fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597690481","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597690481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" a7017fec-5d4d-49d7-8262-3da7786c65fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597693773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597693773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" a7017fec-5d4d-49d7-8262-3da7786c65fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597698024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597698024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" a7017fec-5d4d-49d7-8262-3da7786c65fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597699410","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597699410"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" a7017fec-5d4d-49d7-8262-3da7786c65fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597707880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597707880"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" a7017fec-5d4d-49d7-8262-3da7786c65fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597716947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597716947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 2169c0fb-a002-4844-be46-527cdb937a8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_a-r-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597721258","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597721258"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 2169c0fb-a002-4844-be46-527cdb937a8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_g-i-d"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597725013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597725013"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 2169c0fb-a002-4844-be46-527cdb937a8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-p"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597728273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597728273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 2169c0fb-a002-4844-be46-527cdb937a8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_l-i-g"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597731470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597731470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 2169c0fb-a002-4844-be46-527cdb937a8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_h-z-i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597754924","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597754924"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 2169c0fb-a002-4844-be46-527cdb937a8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_l-a-i"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597760240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597760240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 2169c0fb-a002-4844-be46-527cdb937a8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_e-i-a"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597777483","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597777482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 2169c0fb-a002-4844-be46-527cdb937a8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_ch-n-i"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597780327","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597780327"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 2169c0fb-a002-4844-be46-527cdb937a8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-p-n"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597806459","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597806459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 2169c0fb-a002-4844-be46-527cdb937a8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_v-z-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597812201","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597812200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 2169c0fb-a002-4844-be46-527cdb937a8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_i_v-z-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..22.off2.17__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597826462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597826461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 2169c0fb-a002-4844-be46-527cdb937a8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_i_v-z-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597831765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597831765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 2169c0fb-a002-4844-be46-527cdb937a8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_i_v-z-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597837788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597837788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 2169c0fb-a002-4844-be46-527cdb937a8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_i_v-z-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:I..I.all.10.rand.say.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597845131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597845130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 2169c0fb-a002-4844-be46-527cdb937a8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_i_v-z-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597851596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597851596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 2169c0fb-a002-4844-be46-527cdb937a8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_i_v-z-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597860673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597860673"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 46c86ef0-50a3-4309-a144-abab47dc59fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-k-b"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597864326","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597864325"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 46c86ef0-50a3-4309-a144-abab47dc59fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_d-i-a"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597869979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597869979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 46c86ef0-50a3-4309-a144-abab47dc59fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_t-i-d"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597872980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597872980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 46c86ef0-50a3-4309-a144-abab47dc59fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-e-l"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597876403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597876403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 46c86ef0-50a3-4309-a144-abab47dc59fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_l-y-i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597881351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597881351"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 46c86ef0-50a3-4309-a144-abab47dc59fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_f-i-y"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597885227","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597885227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 46c86ef0-50a3-4309-a144-abab47dc59fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_r-i-a"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597888694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597888694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 46c86ef0-50a3-4309-a144-abab47dc59fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_n-f-i"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597895334","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597895334"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 46c86ef0-50a3-4309-a144-abab47dc59fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-u-e"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597913294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597913294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 46c86ef0-50a3-4309-a144-abab47dc59fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_r-z-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597919046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597919045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 46c86ef0-50a3-4309-a144-abab47dc59fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_i_r-z-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597957770","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597957770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 46c86ef0-50a3-4309-a144-abab47dc59fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_i_r-z-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597957858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597957858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 8e4d2ed3-086f-4a76-9369-ae1129217e4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEMAZANE"," userResponse":" DEMAZANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597963700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597963700"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 8e4d2ed3-086f-4a76-9369-ae1129217e4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597969106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597969106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 8e4d2ed3-086f-4a76-9369-ae1129217e4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597975479","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597975479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 8e4d2ed3-086f-4a76-9369-ae1129217e4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597981228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597981227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" 8e4d2ed3-086f-4a76-9369-ae1129217e4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597991241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597991241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597992283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597992283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597994876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597994876"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597995926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597995926"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597998888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597998888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597999929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597999929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598002868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598002868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598003901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598003901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598006461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598006460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598008237","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598008237"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598010773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598010773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598012405","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598012404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598014931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598014931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598014984","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598014984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598015985","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598015985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598018202","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598018202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598020665","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598020665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598021709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598021708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598024881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598024881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598025917","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598025917"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598028572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598028572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598028804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598028804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598029702","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598029702"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598032370","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598032370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598035048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598035048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598035165","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598035164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598036169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598036169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598038459","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598038459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598041205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598041205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598042837","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598042837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598045425","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598045425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598045574","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598045574"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598046598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598046598"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598049254","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598049254"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598051889","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598051889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598052930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598052930"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598055880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598055880"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598056118","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598056118"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598057006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598057006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598059414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598059414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598061848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598061847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598062889","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598062888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598065803","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598065803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598066839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598066839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598069554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598069554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598069735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598069735"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598070642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598070642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598073203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598073203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598076554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598076554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548598076744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548598076744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_165748"," gameId":" f40dd1e0-6c2b-4b61-92fb-d967a47b9ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}